Even if there was
This is contagious.
Did you throw the scallops at me?
Ahahaha
Did you throw Ceresa's scallops?
This is also maize
terrible
There it was
This one
Hello
Mayutan Association
I'm Mayutan, the leader of the Mayutan Association.
Wow
My name is Mikyun, a member of the association.
Squeaking
I'm Aya, a member of the Mayutan Association.
number 2
This is Mayutan Association member 3 Sacchan.
And now the town is home
Since my hometown is a school, I feel like I'll meet up later.
Telepan fans, please rest assured.
I'm coming
I haven't left yet.
I'll come after this
So today we're going to have a barbecue.
Yay
this
Already outside
Go, go, go!
Under this sky full of sky
we would like to have a barbecue
Why is there a barbecue today?
we are under construction
I won the championship and it was time for the corps showdown.
I want to use these tongs that I received at that time.
So today we had a barbecue.
everyone here
Something like that
Mayutan Association and Mayu Tamura.
everyone is written
Something baked
I'll show you
I think it would be better to separate the birds.
I agree
I would like to find
This is the ingredients for this time.
meat and seafood
There are also hamburgers
That's right
happy
what?
hamburger
Yes, I think I wanted to do this
thank you
So it's a very loose shellfish.
Let's bake and eat right away
yes
Yes
First to toast?
Yeah
Good job
Thank you for your continued support.
thank you
bye bye
Yay
my hair has become darker
I just dyed it
cute
It suits you so well
On the other hand, Miku
You want to dye your hair, right?
That's right, isn't it?
I want to see it
Blonde or something
Suddenly
When I was in elementary school, I also put bread on it.
It's fashionable
I went to the perm wondering if it would make it fluffy.
Oh, was it wrong?
I'm sure I'll die from Gringly after all, right?
So I took a nap at home and came back.
I have memories of
It was some sort of dance, but we did it in elementary school.
I'll give it a little dance perm
I thought the dance would look good, so I did it.
Not really
It was too much
a!
Eh, isn't that Tei-chan?
Oh, it's Tei-chan!
Tei-chan?
Has Corps E4 arrived?
Good, come before you eat.
Hello, this is Teresa Ikeda. thank you.
It’s here, it’s here!
I brought this from school today.
Oh, that's a terrible hamburger.
It's a hell of a hamburger.
I've been addicted to hamburgers lately.
Is that so?
Do you eat it at home?
No, I'll just go.
In the meantime, eat a hamburger at Coco's.
It's cute.
That's amazing.
There's meat at the National Horse Racing Firth.
Cette Blake
tongs
Does anyone eat it?
I also added lessing
It's kind of amazing, the visibility etc.
Did you go out to dinner with the army? It was amazing.
surely
Because this happened
I thought it would be nice if there was something like that.
The day will finally come when I can tell everyone that I went
happy
Is there anything you would like to do with the army?
I've always said I wanted to make goods.
Yeah yeah
Let's all think together
People say they're jealous of the songs I was able to create.
That's fine
There isn't, right?
Because only we have it
There's only what's here in the world
amazing
really amazing
That's amazing
I want to perform it live
I don't know but
I want to see Maitan Association live.
TRUE?
nice
mini live
I want it by genre.
This time's song is
It seems cool though
The gesture was so cute
I can tell you this because I've already seen the unveiling, but it's easy to remember.
Cute Zen-style songs and cool Zen-style songs
It's in between
I want a lot of things
That's right
please
I'm waiting
What are you two doing?Usually
I
what?
picture?
hang on
what?
What was it?
What? What? What?
What? Can I take a picture?
What?
I can't see it
of the screen
Where, where, what?
What where?
everytime
Eat dinner with Aya
no food in mouth
Tell me a little bit
Ah, everyone
ah
Hey Aya everyone
What is this?
Is it seaweed?
That's cute, thank you
It spreads a lot around you in one bite.
So why so much
What did you do? Did it stick to you like this?
He said he was thinking of taking it now.
Then I ate it again and put it on again.
feel like a baby
As a member of Mayutan Association
Azataku
I thought so, but I guess it's just on purpose.
I did it on purpose so that everyone wouldn't get it wrong.
Please don't call me a baby
Because you're angry
My cradle is
Teach me the scallop dance
Hotate
cute
Scallop dancing
What are you doing?
Because it's large, medium and small
I was doing the scallop dance now
That's the famous scallop dance.
A big buzz on SNS
scallop dance
What is that?
picture~
What?Aya, tell me
Hey it's you
tell me this
Look, Tere-chan told me.
I haven't seen the scallop dance yet.
I don't understand the scallop dance
Seeno
Hotate
increased
- Did you attach it? Did the bone come out?
Did the bones come out?
Did Teresa's bones come out?
It's fast after you eat it
- Did the bones come out? Runrun!
- Did a bone come out? Did a bone come out! Did a bone come out?
- A bone came out! A bone came out!
Ogawa-san is really good at coming up with dance ideas.
I hope Mr. Ogawa will be the next choreographer.
- For sure! I would love to have Mr. Ogawa do the next choreography.
- I'd love for you to do the first cute kitten pose there.
Thank you for watching
Can I have that pose that I love?
If Mayu says so, I'll do it.
Really?
I'm coming
This one
yes
my favorite pose
Thank you Teru-san
thank you
Thank you Teru
Amazing
terrible
too large amount
Meat Masa
I'll enjoy having this
delicious?
Maybe we made it ourselves
You gave me something that suits me.
delicious?
This is Rito
Ah, economic litho
I can't get Rito out of my head lately.
When I'm taking a bath or drying my head
litori litori litho
regrettable
I wonder why I can't get Rito out of my head and not Gundan's song.
Now is the time to sell
You know, it's really addictive.
It becomes a habit, isn't it?
What's our song?
Don't you wear cat ears?
That's why I actually wanted to wear it during the mini live.
But I couldn't say it
I want to wear it
I definitely want to put on Sotsukon and play that song.
Will you do it?
Yours? Not mine?
I want to use it on my computer too
Then, if you've graduated by then, call me.
Will you stand on stage?
I really said it
It's crazy now
It was super light! Stand up!
I felt like I was standing up.
It's like going and going
I'll ride it just in case YouTube
Yeah! That's right
in this place
brackets
Depends on your mood that day
I don't miss it
So yes
I also want to make T-shirts for the army.
Ah! I want to win!
I want to make a corps T-shirt too.
I want it to look kind of stylish.
Is the theme color of the corps yellow? After all
Eh, but I actually prefer pink.
but
Before it's taken away, it's pink and it's early.
Yay pink pink
I'm listening to everyone's wishes, oh
That means it's been around since 2000, right? It's already limited to the Maitan Association.
What about Jamayu? I guess it's actually pink.
I like that it's stylish.
Somehow purple
Something with a twist
It's like Tawakoise Blue.
emerald green or something
Kind of like Sky
I wish there was something like sky blue.
I also wanted to make it pink somehow
strawberry milk
cute
Isn't it cute?
strawberry milk
Strawberry milk color properly
That's the name
amazing
Base clip?
Like Yakiniku brown
what up?
hormone beige
terrible
The color is stylish though
Hormone beige is terrible
What's wrong with the beige costume?
Yukeret
Cholegigri
I want to make costumes too.I want to make them.
We want to perform live wearing the costumes that we made ourselves. We even wrote the music and lyrics.
Hmm, not composing the music, but writing the lyrics? We want to compose the song ourselves.
Hmm? I already made the scallops. I won't go.
We have a lot of things we want to do, which is a good thing.
So today is that
I had a barbecue at the Mori-san Association.
barbecue
I was able to talk about many dreams,
I would like to do my best to make this a reality.
Everyone, please subscribe to the channel and give it a high rating.
bye bye